<resources>
    <string name="app_name">iVolley</string>
    <string name="slogan">Spike into the Volleyball lifestyle</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">
         Es un deporte que se juega con una pelota y en el que dos equipos, integrados por seis jugadores cada uno, se enfrentan sobre una área de juego separada por una red central. El objetivo del juego es pasar el balón por encima de la red, logrando que llegue al suelo del campo contrario mientras el equipo adversario intenta impedir simultáneamente que lo consiga, forzándolo a errar en su intento. Surge una fase de ataque en un equipo cuando intenta que el balón toque el suelo del campo contrario mientras que en el otro equipo surge una fase de defensa intentando impedirlo.
    </string>

    <string name="volleyball_rules">
        · 6 players on a team, 3 on the front row and 3 on the back row\n
        · There is a maximum of three hits per side\n
        · Player may not hit the ball twice in succession (A block is not considered a hit)\n
        · Ball may be played off the net during a volley and on a serve\n
        · A ball hitting a boundary line is ‘in’\n
        · A ball is ‘out’ if it hits:\n
            - an antennae,\n
            - the floor completely outside the court,\n
            - any of the net or cables outside the antennae,\n
            - the referee stand or pole,\n
            - the ceiling of the venue\n
        · It is legal to contact the ball with any part of a players body\n
        · It is illegal to catch, hold, or throw the ball\n
        · If two or more players contact the ball at the same time, it is considered one play and either player involved may make the next contact (provided the next contact isn’t the teams 4th hit)\n
        · A player cannot block or attack a serve from on or inside the 3 meter line\n
        · After the serve, front line players may switch positions at the net\n
        · If a team has five players they will have a ghost position and when that position is serving the team will lose the point and serve.\n
        · The referee/duty crew is made up of two refs, line judges and a scorekeeper.\n
    </string>
</resources>